Good morning!
It's Minamiko!
They're going to show everyone's footage over there.
That's why there are a lot of cameras there.
Basically, there are a lot of cameras over there.
I'm often overtaken over there, so...
I'll leave it to you.
Yes!
Keep your eyes on the road and keep glancing at it.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Good morning, Music Original.
Thank you very much for this valuable experience today.
I'll do my best to make the stadium a great place to be.
I look forward to working with you today.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
Please give my regards to you.
Thank you very much. I look forward to working with you on the show. Best regards. Eeeeeeeeee me.
Wow!!! I'm so happy!
Looking forward to it!
Human football
Human football.
But for today...
Practice prep.
Preparation for the style of play.
I've divided it up a bit.
Oh, wait! You're so cute!
So cute!
Wait, it's cute.
It's so cute!
He's so cute! Please, please, pretty! Cute! Cute!
Pretty!
Cute!
Bye-bye.
Cute! He's so cute! I'll keep it open!
Nice to meet you.
Wow!
She's so cute!
Oh, no!
He's so cute.
Oh, it's so cute.
Oh, this is the best! Oh, OK cute cute cute awesome.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'm off then.
Three, two, one.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Sumi's cute.
Sumiroku.
I just had a rehearsal with you.
It's the first time we're really performing in a stadium.
It's a big place and I'm very nervous.
It's a really rare opportunity.
And here I am! My first time!
Let's go!
I'm going to do my best! Looking forward to it!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, OK, OK.
Thank you very much.
Pleasure to meet you
Nice to meet you
Please, please, please.
What, what, what, what?
It's so cute.
It made me feel at home.
I got three shots with her.
Oh, my God...
A flower treasure.
I want to make her a flower treasure.
I'm about to go on stage.
I don't want to be nervous.
I'll do my best to make it exciting.
I'm off now.
Something like this...
I don't know...
When I tried to show her face...
Hold it like this.
Make it a little cuter.
But I don't know...
I like it when you hold it like this.
I like it this way, too.
It's cute.
Good work, sir.
After this...
I'm going to give a performance.
I'm going to perform.
But we're rehearsing.
It's my first time in a stadium.
It's a really big stadium.
It's a big stadium.
I'm so nervous, it's awful.
I'm wearing a really cute outfit.
It's a very precious experience, so I'm going to do my best.
I'll do my best with Mr. Devilo.
I'm maxed out with nerves.
I'm so nervous, I'm shaking.
I'm shaking and nervous, but I've never had a chance like this before.
I'm really looking forward to it.
You're so cute!
I'm so nervous!
I'm so nervous.
It won't take you long to get there.
Good.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it... I can do it!
You can do it! I can do it!
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's all do our best!
Aimin! It's okay!
It's okay!
Whoa! Kecho!
Speak up, speak up, speak up, please.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen, we are the New Leake Olds Eye.
Pleasure to meet you.
Thank you very much.
And now, please come.
Smile and be merry, my dear.
Always singing, always singing, always singing, the red colour, the red colour, the red colour, the red colour, the red colour, the red colour, the red colour, the red colour.
But today, too, I'm going to be in your eyes.
Let's all the people of the palace and the people of Mt. Takao be excited to the very end.
Don't forget today without meeting each other.
The days when you and I will change.
I've delivered everything.
Now, let's hang on to this... but which is it? Even if you say so...
Reach out your hand.
One more time.
Not love, not love.
Sing of your dreams.
Forever
Let's go to love
Thick, reach me
Let me sleep in your brain
I don't want to see everything more than anything else that opens up to a lie, neee neee neee
Today's performance was us, the Newarry Ghosts.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, here comes the mini-form!
This one, too.
It's number 99.
Some of the players have the number 99.
I thought we were the same.
Thank you very much for this precious experience, my first time to play football in a stadium.
The supporters of both teams are very powerful.
I like the support.
It's fun! I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
I've had the chance to watch the game at the stadium a few times with my dad.
It's amazing.
I was just looking at these symbols with the members and
I've been looking at these uniforms and looking them up.
First of all, I wondered where the word Jubilo comes from, so I looked it up.
It means ‘ventilation’ in Portuguese and Spanish.
And what's that, the moon and sun star?
It's a reference to the moon, sun and star, which is the bird of Shizuoka Prefecture?
The bird's call is Shizuoka Prefecture's bird?
The bird's call is ‘Tsukihi Hoshi Hui Hui’.
The bird's call is ‘Tsukihi Hoshi Hui Hui’, which means ‘Moon, Sun and Star, Hui Hui’.
That's where it comes from.
I looked it up.
For today.
I liked it a lot earlier.
But I didn't know enough about it to say.
I didn't really know much about it.
I was learning a bit.
I really enjoyed what you just showed me up there.
I'm looking forward to seeing the second half after that.
We will be discoing the gym disco and venue disco. It's really great, we were able to perform a little earlier, but the venue was really hot and so were we.
We'll do our best to liven things up a little bit.
We'll do our best. Half-time!
We'll do our best at half-time.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. You're gone, you're gone, you're gone, you're gone, there's a place to change the world.
It's started perfectly.
In your previous life, you were merciless.
Be the shape you bring.
Surrounded by your body.
I'll lend it to you
Fuze in happy
It was the Miyagi duo! Thank you very much! Congratulations, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so I've just had my half-time performance.
I was really nervous because I was just starting out.
I was so nervous, but I was so happy to put my hand down.
Really, the supporters of Jubilo Iwata, too.
I think that the supporters of Jubilo-Iwata are also in a state of ‘what are we? I think we were in a state like that,
But everyone was really warm, and even people who didn't know us joined in and got excited with us,
We also had fans who usually support us come and see us,
We hope that we can continue to complete the project and support you as hard as we can.
Thank you very much. I hope you will support us. Thank you very much. All the members of the team,
I was able to have a great experience of cheering for Mr Suzuki's game,
It was a great experience for me,
I was very nervous before the game and at half-time,
The most important thing was that we enjoyed ourselves,
We did our best with the feeling that we could enjoy ourselves and cheer with the players,
I hope you enjoy the game afterwards too.
I was able to play Ruby Newmont for the first time today, which I should have done before when it was no longer on YouTube.
I'm really happy!
I'm so happy, really happy happy happy happy.
Even though I'm wearing this.
I feel like I'm one of the players.
Confidence.
That's great.
It's been a lot of fun, it's been empowering.
Thank you so much for the experience.
It was a great day.
Thank you very much.
The second half of the season is great.
You should see it.
Amazing, amazing, amazing, amazing.
Oh, my God.
Since a few minutes ago...
I can hear you all...
I'm hearing a lot of cheering.
I was wondering what was going on.
I've been wondering what's going on.
I've been here for quite a while now.
I'd like to go and see it as soon as possible after this.
We, the people who were performing at that time, did our best.
We hope that people will think that we've become such amazing idols.
We Miyaji and I will do our best to make you think that.
We Miyaji and I will do our best.
I look forward to your continued support.
Thank you very much.